CHAD LISCINSKY

Relocating to Portland Oregon | 415 505 5859 | chadliscinsky@gmail.com | LinkedIn | chadliscinsky.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Account Management, B2B Sales and Customer Success Professional with a proven record of positive results executing strategic plans to meet company objectives. Highly experienced creating essential partnerships and lasting relationships with current and prospective clients. Technology focused, problem solver and here to make the workplace an exciting and inspiring environment to thrive in. My passion for growth, success and new technology combined with my creative drive keeps customers engaged while bringing their visions to life.

WORK EXPERIENCE

DIRECTOR OF SALES | ENCORE EVENT TECHNOLOGIES, SAN FRANCISCO, CA

June 2017 - Present

- Lead and mentor a skilled team of Account Executives generating a 17%+ Increase in overall revenues while surpassing all personal quotas
- Successfully maintained business for over 30 Enterprise level accounts with individual overall revenues ranging from \$100k 400k annually.
- Develop and execute a highly successful B2B engagement strategy that proactively maintains customer satisfaction leading to a consistent customer capture and retention rate of 94%+
- Engage and manage full B2B sales cycles ranging from 6 months to two years
- Integrate technical expertise and demonstrations of product with industry best practices for all customers leading to the positive execution of large complex events for top Enterprise clientele
- Interface with Senior Leadership to help strategize and create beneficial customer facing marketing materials for all partners
- Maintain and enhance customer satisfaction by providing ongoing, proactive support throughout the customer life cycle and beyond

SENIOR ACCOUNT EXECUTIVE | PSAV, SAN FRANCISCO, CA

June 2014 – May 2017

- Managed the Enterprise tech, corporate and association business utilizing a 360-degree sales approach ensuring capture and retention rates of 90%+
- Consistently top 3rd or above revenue generating Account Executive in the west super region with average yearly revenue totals of \$3.5 million+
- Develop new business from lead stage while engaging sales cycles from 1 month to a year
- Worked directly with clients and producers to develop and provide them with new concepts for their events including CAD development and production schedule securing flawless events

INSIDE SALES ASSOCIATE | TICKETFLY SAN FRANCISCO, CA

March 2012 - June 2014

- Prospected leads within specific verticals to provide the senior sales team with qualified appointments averaging 20 solid appointments per week
- Responsible for all B2B sales activities, from lead generation to signed agreements with a consistent sales cycle of 1 – 6 months
- Developed and maintained a complete database of leads and clients within Salesforce CRM
- Demonstrated product knowledge to allow for effective presentation of Ticketfly's software and services leading to an overall increase in demand for the platform.
- Maintained accurate records of all sales and prospecting activities including sales calls, demonstrations, closed sales and follow up activities
- Average call rate of 60+ qualified leads per week with 10+ demonstrations presented

ACCOUNT EXECUTIVE | SWANK AUDIO VISUALS, SAN FRANCISCO, CA

May 2007 - March 2012

- Coordinated over 500+ events with a consistent 10%+ YOY increase in overall revenues
- Worked directly with Technical Directors for initial event conception
- Managed client's budgets ranging from 25k to 250k for all audio visual and IT needs necessary for their events
- Achieved sales targets on a consistent basis

SKILL HIGHLIGHTS

Customer SuccessHTML5Account ManagementLeadershipB2B SalesCustomer ExperienceProblem solvingSalesforce CRMBusiness DevelopmentRelationship BuildingCSS3Results

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

New England Institute of Art
Bachelor of Arts, Audio Production
Swank Audio Visuals – Rainmakers Sales Program | Certified
PSAV – Engage Sales Training | Certified
Encore Event Technologies – e360 Sales Training | Certified

ACTIVITIES

Music, Film, Travel, Production, Audio, Computer Technology, Outdoors and Food